[
    {"question":"Which player has played a record of 21 World Cup matches for Argentina?", "answer":"Diego Maradona"},
    {"question":"Which player has scored the first goal for Australia at the World Cups?", "answer":"Tim Cahill"},
    {"question":"Which player was the Argentina top scorer at the 2018 World Cup?", "answer":"Sergio Agüero"},
    {"question":"Which player didn't score for Argentina in the 4-3 loss to France in the Round of 16 at the 2018 World Cup?", "answer":"Lionel Messi"},
    {"question":"Which player scored the winning goal for France against Portugal at the 2006 World Cup semi-final?", "answer":"Zinedine Zidane"},
    {"question":"Which player in 2002 scored the fastest goal in World Cup history just 10.8 seconds after kick-off?", "answer":"Hakan Sukur"},
    {"question":"Which Russian player scored twice in the opening match against Saudi Arabia at the 2018 World Cup?", "answer":"Denis Cheryshev"},
    {"question":"Which team was the first to win three World Cup trophies?", "answer":"Brazil"},
    {"question":"Which player is Brazil's World Cup leading scorer?", "answer":"Ronaldo"},
    {"question":"Which player has the most appearances for Netherlands at the World Cups?", "answer":"Wesley Sneijder"},
    {"question":"Which player has the most appearances as captain at the World Cup?", "answer":"Rafael Márquez"},
    {"question":"Which player is the oldest one to appear on a World Cup game with 45 years and 161 days?", "answer":"Essam El Hadary"}

  ]